all right everyone out of the
car
thanks for bringing me along guys with
me coming along you're gonna have the
best 4th of July ever of course Schnucks
it's not a holiday unless I'm spending
it with my best bud
hahahahaha thanks man now Charles I'll
be right across the street getting my
hair done
if anything happens don't be afraid to
come get me I'll be here to pick you all
up in about an hour
here's my credit card use it to buy
whatever fireworks the kids want yeah
yeah saluton Elena saw how much money is
on thicker doormen well there's about 45
on the card although you only need to
use about $20 $20 woman do you know how
much can soft-bodied call what wait
that's it Charles you're not buying beer
we're here to buy fireworks for the kids
now if you excuse me I really need to go
get my hair done I'll be back soon
Charles you are hurting my wrist
you're hurting me Charles stop it
I don't need this catch you later
come on Uncle Chuck let's go
already
I want to see all the fireworks ah calm
your tits Sonja the Phaedo works want me
going anywhere yo stupid rotor suey
okay keys before a yo rune of topic OD
on fear works in gonna nail yo a dog
atera yo mo terrace here em er credit
cards and very specific instruction
tattini l tofu yo first off I say sido a
cannoli oseh tote a loaf when Tia know
my Gino or Pharoah won $20 what the hell
could we buy with just $20 yeah we need
forty at least old man this is
no no kids this is your motors money so
we're sticking by a rule a Tamaki su
away he told Mona Shorty also connect
with a lottery there today SOT oh yeah
limit on whatever yo oh boy $2 new ha it
don't work like that
I don't even spend that little on toilet
paper to wipe my smelly butt Knuckles
come down it's not even your money
it's our mums Manic I'm doing this for
you you guys need to learn to stand up
to this sad old man can't you see he's
just trying to take advantage of you he
thinks that just because he's your uncle
you're his look I finna today
either ya limit happy not well
it's something I guess come on
we're outta here
holy bro come check out the sweet
firework I found
no way is that really what I think it is
you bet your big bless it is bro
you
man this really sucks
what do you mean Knuckles what do you
think this $3.00 limit is ridiculous I'm
going to go find Sonic and Manic
hopefully they found something good
no way is that really what I think it is
it sure is nuts the Firecracker 5000 I
saw a commercial for it on TV they're
saying that it's the best firework
uglier
we did it boys we found the perfect
firework this is going to be the best
4th of July ever oh did you guys find
something interesting yet we did we just
found the best firework ever best
firework ever I don't know about that it
doesn't look like anything special to me
to pick a level woman they have no idea
just how much more badass some fireworks
can be all right guys let's go find
Uncle Chuck so we can check out and
Sonya whatever you plan on getting put
it back woman like you who don't
understand how fireworks work have no
right to be buying them in the first
place today Joe KITT sorry Eva Bello
kena yo before yo are you ready to check
out no yeah we are and we even found the
best firework in the world vest
fado or Quintero Rubio's I will cut the
most beso Metin
kids I'm sorry to burst your bubble but
you see sway over the priests limit well
yet we know it's a bit much but we
thought that maybe we could put
everything else back then bro look out
oh my God you're up but you just
punched a kid old man why it's your
messed up in the head damn look at
on the blood oh my God oh
he ain't know yet what tomorrow well ano
idiot
that's a kid not a you dumb
and midgets earned from Mordor those are
hobbits when you're old man
enjoy Joaquina minute don't wanna worry
you can't go anywhere mom said you were
supposed to stay and watch us where do
you guys think he's going it looks like
he's heading into the liquor store
he really didn't just go home did he
kids
I'm here to pick you all up Hut why are
you kids all just standing around
where are your fireworks where's Uncle
Chuck you should be more worried about
where you car is woman my car kids what
does he mean he means exactly what he
says mama Uncle Chuck stole the family
car and drove home yeah he really hauled
ass he went home there's no way we're
practically 20 miles away from home
Sonja give me your phone
come on Charles weather hello you pick
up your damn phone already
system through the back
Mon what Ewald domingo tota if she
went with AER soul
what the did he just hang up on me
woman what Domingo you want in Buzzi
Charles can pick us up no no Charles we
need to get home get over here
no well how do you expect us to get home
when you took the car with you you're
what lives put them Tosa
yeah you're rich that step will be Frey
you're green it will be boy oh yeah
put the money Conte for a tour why do
you want to talk to him cause Domingo
twitch here Manic your uncle says he
wants to speak to you about something
you just farted in the phone alright
everyone that's a sign that we're
walking home put your things back and
let's go
huh
holy I need a chili dog I'm so
tired can we rest for a bit guys
come on bro pick up the pace we are only
about 20 minutes away from home oh yeah
I guess you do have a point okay let's
go
you
oh good day everyone what are you all
doing out here
I expected you all to be at home playing
with some cheap $30 fireworks
oh hello Bart levy good afternoon babe
yes but what are you doing out here
my Beach should not be walking through
this kind of heat oh well you see
Bartleby while we were out buying
fireworks our uncle kind of stole the
car and drove home without us so now
we're forced to walk home well that just
won't do up in my limo and I'll give you
all a ride wow this is so awesome thanks
Bart let the inside of the limo is so
big wow I can't believe this
Bart lebih has so much money Wow Sonic
your boyfriend is the best I can't
believe you get banged in the ass by a
guy like that
you
Oh leave a Wotton Erte salimos owner
oh boy yirou is low applique or really
disappointed in me I understand Yolo a
disappointed a meto Yaiba be no real
jerk I'll die buuut Domingo yote in
Tioga skull for give em a uri a Leontes
del Meridian oh sorry am I oh no about
the skies what you think should we
forgive him
of course we aren't going to let him
that dumb just wants to ride in
the limo sorry Charles we talked it over
and we forgive you
but nobody wants you in the limo
you know I was really hoping that
we could watch the fireworks together
like this I am really glad I could spend
this holiday with you by my side
you